All the fun of college. None of the education.
Old School is a comedy film directed by Todd Phillips.
Three friends attempt to recapture their glory days by
opening up a fraternity near their alma mater.
Mitch, played by Luke Wilson.
Frank, played by Will Ferrell.
Beanie, played by Vince Vaughn.
Pritchard, played by Jeremy Piven.
Nicole, played by Ellen Pompeo.
Heidi, played by Juliette Lewis.
Old School is a 2003 American comedy film directed
and co-written by Todd Phillips.
The film stars Luke Wilson, Will Ferrell, and Vince Vaughn as depressed men in their thirties who seek to relive
their college days by starting a fraternity, and the tribulations they encounter in doing so.
Old School was produced by The Montecito Picture Company and
released by DreamWorks Pictures on February 21, 2003.
The film received mixed reviews from critics, and grossed
$87.1 million worldwide on a $24 million budget.
The film explores themes of infidelity, group sex,
college, male friendship, beer.
The tone is lighthearted.